Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Iconographic Collection, 1848-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Thomas Veres Photographs and Negatives, 1963-1996 and undated, (60 boxes)
  - Negatives, 1963-1996 and undated>
    - 3-20,21,30,31-92. Naomi Schwartz (Box TV58)
    - 3-24-92. Judy Diruzza (Box TV58)
    - 3-25-92. Make A Wish--Central Park (Box TV58)
    - 3-26-92. Group (Direct) Sonya (Box TV58)
    - 3-27,28-92. Izabelle Albaneze (Box TV58)
    - 3-38 to 49-92. Direct biographicals (Box TV58)
    - 4-1-92. Gerry Watson (Box TV58)
    - 4-2,3-92. Media-White Pea Award (Box TV58)
    - 4-6-92. Jane Plant (Box TV58)
    - 4-9-92. Art Work (no photographs available) (Box TV58)
    - 4-10,11-92. Jeff Bodenmann (Box TV58)
    - 4-10,11-92. Susan Popper (Box TV58)
    - 4-12-92. Tom Groves (Box TV58)
    - 4-12-92. 5 different displays (color) (no photographs available) (Box TV58)
    - 1-1-94. Kelly Clark media party (Box TV58)
    - 1-2 to 13-94. PDP studio brochure (Box TV58)
    - 1-15-94. Christmas party 1993 care (Box TV58)
    - 1-16 to 22-94. PDP studio brochure (Box TV58)
    - 1-25,26,27,28-94. Annette Malane, Penny Kowitt, Sandy Chorazy, Nanci Schwartz (Box TV58)
    - 1-29-94. PDP party (Box TV58)
    - 1-30,31-94. Blood drive I, II (Box TV58)
    - 1-32,33,34,35,36,37,38,39,40-94. New Business portraits (Box TV58)
    - 1-41-94. Elizabeth Holland (no photographs available) (Box TV58)
    - 1-42-94. Tutor Juggel (Box TV58)
    - 1-43-94. Producers (Box TV58)
    - 1-44,45-94. Seth Romanon Port.-San Francisco (Box TV58)
    - 1-46-94. Film makers (Box TV58)
    - 1-47,48-94. United fund (no photographs available) (Box TV58)
    - 2-1,2-94. Ignaczio Puccio biographical portrait (Box TV58)
    - 2-1,2-94. Nat Rosen biographical portrait (Box TV58)
    - 2-3,4-94. Charles Generally biographical portrait (Box TV58)
    - 2-3,4,5,6-94. Al Navaro Kathleen Senett, Aaron Simkin, Gina Furgele (Box TV58)
    - 2-5,6-94. Michael Hart biographical portrait (Box TV58)
    - 2-7,8-94. Sue Berkowitz (Box TV58)
    - 2-9-94. Jim Patterson (Box TV58)
    - 2-9,10-94. Richard Di Lallo biographical (Box TV59)
    - 2-10-94. Big Idea (no photographs available) (Box TV59)
    - 2-11,12-94. Tom Groves portrait (Box TV59)
    - 2-12,13-94. Bob Schutze, Frank Woei (no photographs available) (Box TV59)
    - 2-14-94. Secretaries Day (Box TV59)
    - 2-15-94. Bring Your Daughter (Box TV59)
    - 2-17,18-94. Talent Show (Box TV59)
    - 2-19-94. Environment books (no photographs available) (Box TV59)
    - 2-20-94. Eyes on Thompson--Peter Hughes (Box TV59)
    - 2-21-94. Tutor lunch (Box TV59)
    - 2-22-94. Steve Cody studio (Box TV59)
    - 2-23-94. Irene Hansen (Box TV59)
    - 2-25-94. Malcolm End (Box TV59)
    - 2-26-94. Edward Moed (Box TV59)
    - 2-27,28-94. Marty Rose award lunch (Grand Hyatt) (Box TV59)
    - 2-29,30-94. Susan Berkowitz portrait (Box TV59)
    - 2-32,33,34-94. Rothann Richert, Emile Council, Cynthia De Rosier (Box TV59)
    - 2-36,37-94. Blood drive I,II (Box TV59)
    - 2-38-94. Mooving party (Box TV59)
    - 3-14-94. Ruthann Richart II biographical (Box TV59)
    - 3-15,16-94. Marty Susz biographical portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-17,18-94. Kelly Clark biographical portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-19,20-94. Manning Rubin biographical portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-21,22-94. Kendall Crolius biographical portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-23-94. Michael Hart II biographical (Box TV59)
    - 3-24,25-94. Peter Leinroth biographical portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-26,27-94. Louis Jones biographical portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-32-94. 420 Lexington 11th-floor (Box TV59)
    - 3-33,34,35,36,37-94. Nancy Faua, Amy Rosenberg, R. Richert, Neerja Narayanan, Jim Newell (Box TV59)
    - 3-38-94. Kelly Clark biographical II (Box TV59)
    - 3-39,40-94. Chris DeGuzman biographical portrait B (Box TV59)
    - 3-41, 42-94. Kendall Crolius II biographical II portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-43-94. Peter Leinroth biographical II (Box TV59)
    - 3-46-94. Mitch Orfuss: Direct biographical I (Box TV59)
    - 3-48 to 51-94. J. Berman, L. Margulis, I. Baer, Paul Tarantanella (Box TV59)
    - 3-52,53,54-94. Rob Santangelo I, Rob Santangelo II, Susan Sullivan (Box TV59)
    - 3-55,56-94. Make-A-Wish (Box TV59)
    - 3-57-94. Eyes on Thompson--Jerry Dominic (Box TV59)
    - 3-58-94. Direct group (summer outings) (Box TV59)
    - 3-59-94. Alan Goltz studio (Box TV59)
    - 3-60,61-94. Jean Brown studio, Ashley Adams studio (Box TV59)
    - 3-62-94. Barbara Singer N.B. portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-64,65-94. Nancy Hallberg biographical portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-66,67-94. Kathy Stevens biographical portrait (Box TV59)
    - 4-1-94. Mitch Orfuss: Direct biographical II (Box TV59)
    - 4-2-94. Eyes on Thompson--London: Jasper Shelbourne, Dominic Procter (Box TV59)
    - 4-3-94. Jim Foster (magazine) (Box TV59)
    - 4-4,5,6-94. Rich Fisher, 2 studio setup, college dorm (no photographs available) (Box TV59)
    - 4-7,8-94. YMCA Emily Schwartzenruber, Ron Burns (Box TV59)
    - 4-9-94. Larry Volpi studio (Box TV59)
    - 4-10,11-94. New V.P. party (Box TV59)
    - 4-12,13,14,15-94. Annette Stover, May Armstrong, Carrie Craglyaile, Debbie Kowarz (Box TV59)
    - 4-16-94. Domingo Perez senior V.P (Box TV59)
    - 4-18-94. Michael Hawkins--Direct (Box TV59)
    - 4-19-94. Warner-Lambert International group (Box TV59)
    - 4-21-94. Salvador Dali art (Box TV59)
    - 1-6-95. Margaret Bambakas, Linda Rovero, Andrea Lando: group Marty Susz (Box TV59)
    - 1-7,8-95. Volutair Christmas party (Box TV59)
    - 1-9 to 31-95. PDP portrait brochure (Box TV59)
    - 1-32-95. PDP NIT (Box TV59)
    - 1-33-95. Blood drive (Box TV59)
    - 1-34-95. Blood posters color (no photographs available) (Box TV59)
    - 1-35-95. Barry Lott portrait (Box TV59)
    - 1-36-95. Jean Pool portrait (Box TV59)
    - 1-37,38,39-95. John Clinton biographical portrait (Box TV59)
    - 1-41-95. Bell Atlantic group (Box TV59)
    - 1-43-95. 4 different color panel for Italy (no photographs available) (Box TV59)
    - 1-44-95. Scott International meeting (Box TV59)
    - 1-46-95. Domingo Perez portrait (Box TV59)
    - 1-47-95. Gail Heany portrait (Box TV59)
    - 1-48-95. Tony Incaltera NB portrait (Box TV59)
    - 1-49-95. John Mossawr NB portrait (Box TV59)
    - 1-50-95. Karen Prober NB portrait (Box TV59)
    - 1-51-95. United Fund kick-off party (Box TV59)
    - 2-1-95. Burt Manning (no photographs available) (Box TV59)
    - 2-2-95. Janine Prestegaard portrait (Box TV59)
    - 2-3,4-95. Secretaries Day (Box TV59)
    - 2-5-95. Bob Schrijuer portrait (Box TV59)
    - 2-7-95. Tutor--chorus (Box TV59)
    - 2-8,9-95. RSVP Tavern on the G: Janine Prestegaard (Box TV59)
    - 2-10-95. Maria Gianoutsos portrait (Box TV59)
    - 2-11-95. Jolie Defeis portrait (Box TV59)
    - 2-12-95. David May portrait (Box TV59)
    - 2-13-95. John Pearson studio portrait (Box TV59)
    - 2-14-95. Mark Fenske studio portrait (Box TV59)
    - 2-15,16-95. Blood drive I, II (Box TV59)
    - 3-1-95. Corp. running group (Box TV59)
    - 3-3-95. James Vincent portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-4-95. Midge Kyler portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-5-95. Kellog breakfast (Box TV59)
    - 3-6-95. Susaan Machtiger portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-8-95. Laura Katz portrait (Box TV59)
    - 3-9 to 17-95. Weight Watchers: Jane Plant, Paul Salisbury, Gina Battafaco, Leann Davis, Evelyn Joice, Linda Goldstein, Allison Rosenberg, Megwin Finegan, Heidi Young (Box TV59)
    - 3-18-95. Weight Watchers box still (no photographs available) (Box TV59)
    - 3-19-95. Eyes on Thompson Jerry Dominus (Box TV59)
    - 3-20,21,22,23-95. Heinekin: Adam Kanner, Matt Dowsher, Karen Prober, Karin Kaplan (Box TV59)
    - 3-24,25-95. Make-A-Wish Central Park (Box TV59)
    - 3-27-95. Heineken decorations (Box TV59)
    - 4-12-95. Ron Capello, Denis Riney (Box TV59)
    - 4-3-95. Liz Coples portrait (Box TV59)
    - 4-4-95. Claudia Rose portrait (Box TV59)
    - 4-9,10-95. Water Cooler still (Box TV59)
    - 4-5-95. DeBeers headshots 27 people (no photographs available) (Box TV59)
    - 4-11,12-95. 420, 466 Buildings, Tim Hages (no photographs available) (Box TV59)
    - 4-13,14-95. Young Creatives w/ Susan Giannino (Box TV59)
    - 4-15-95. Tom Ferrara portrait (Box TV59)
    - 4-17-95. Jeff De Joseph portrait (Box TV59)
    - 4-18-95. Brad Mintz portrait (Box TV59)
    - 4-19-95. Nat Rosen portrait (Box TV59)
    - 4-20-95. Rick Glickman portrait (Box TV60)
    - 4-21-95. Michael Gross portrait (Box TV60)
    - 4-22-95. Elizabeth Gildersleeve portrait (Box TV60)
    - 4-23-95. Lynn Diamond portrait (Box TV60)
    - 4-24-95. Walter Ife portrait (Box TV60)
    - 4-25-95. Bryan Johnston portrait (Box TV60)
    - 1-1-96. Dororthy Marcus (Box TV60)
    - 1-2-96. Christmas party 1995 (Box TV60)
    - 1-4-96. Richard Pollet portrait (Box TV60)
    - 1-5,6-96. De Beers Bart Boydston studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-7,8-96. Ron Dean studio, De Beers (Box TV60)
    - 1-9,10-96. De Beers, Pat Henneberly studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-11,12-96. Barbara Hatht studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-13-96. Bob Verbeck VP studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-14-96. Chris Vilante VP studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-15,16-96. Blood drive I, II (Box TV60)
    - 1-17-96. Brad Mintz color (no photographs available) (Box TV60)
    - 1-18-96. Rona Oberman, Partner (Box TV60)
    - 1-19-96. Bob Shea, Partner (Box TV60)
    - 1-20,21-96. Kathy Beall portrait (Box TV60)
    - 1-22,23-96. Preston Foy portrait (Box TV60)
    - 1-24,25-96. Bob Wheeler portrait (Box TV60)
    - 1-26,27-96. Gene Laroff portrait (Box TV60)
    - 1-28,29-96. Rachel Rosin (Box TV60)
    - 1-30-96. Kellog International meeting (Box TV60)
    - 1-31-96. Peter Geary Partner (Box TV60)
    - 1-32-96. Stacy Style Partner studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-33-96. Liza Stein studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-35-96. Burt Manning b&w transfer to color (no photographs available) (Box TV60)
    - 1-36-56-96. PDP brochure (Box TV60)
    - 1-57,58-96. PDP party (Box TV60)
    - 1-60-96. United Fund party (Box TV60)
    - 1-61-96. Lucy Purdy portrait (Box TV60)
    - 1-62-96. Jill Kossoff portrait (Box TV60)
    - 1-63-96. Judy Ritensky portrait (Box TV60)
    - 1-64-96. Wess Matt portrait (Box TV60)
    - 1-65-96. Kurt Meinen portrait (Box TV60)
    - 1-66-96. John Zissmos portrait, Partner (Box TV60)
    - 1-67-96. Gina Moorhead studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-68-96. Gina Furgele studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-69-96. Audrey Delgrosso studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-70-96. Alberto Ferrer studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-71-96. Linda Goldstein studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-72-96. Anne Wilson studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-73-96. James Kloiber studio (Box TV60)
    - 1-74-96. Kristin Paulus studio (Box TV60)
    - 2-1-96. Tim Thom portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-2-96. Sheryl Max portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-3,4,5,6-96. Laura Bowning, Michelle Carabello, Kenel Restiro, Elaine Kim (Box TV60)
    - 2-7-96. Norm Macmaster portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-8-96. Connie Maloy portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-9-96. Sheryl Prince (Box TV60)
    - 2-10-96. Nancy Faua (Box TV60)
    - 2-11-96. Bill Treuedi (Box TV60)
    - 2-12-96. Sue Bernard Direct biographical (Box TV60)
    - 2-13-96. Eillen Lyons (Box TV60)
    - 2-14-96. Maria Feigenson Direct biographical (Box TV60)
    - 2-15-96. Lee Margolis (Box TV60)
    - 2-16-96. David Sciascia II portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-17-96. Ayn Bree Sheahan (Box TV60)
    - 2-18,19-96. Secretaries Day (Box TV60)
    - 2-20-96. DeBeers Breakfast (Box TV60)
    - 2-21-96. Evelyn Joyce portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-22-96. Jennifer Wishnie portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-23-96. Neeraja Nadayanan portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-24-96. Rob Rothschild (Box TV60)
    - 2-25-96. Orielle Duval (Box TV60)
    - 2-26-96. Andrea Halbersadt portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-27-96. Rachel Treitelman-Rosin portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-28-96. Lynn Diamond portrait, De Beers (Box TV60)
    - 2-29-96. David Sciascia biographical portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-30-96. Connie Marsala portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-31-96. Christine Hoffman portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-32-96. Jason Valentias portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-33-96. Tom O'Connel portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-34-96. Victoria Brown (Box TV60)
    - 2-35-96. Eloisa Pena portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-36-96. Joe Pantigoso portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-37-96. Karen Silverstein portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-38-96. Bio studio portraits Angela Saunders (Box TV60)
    - 2-39-96. Brad Mintz for magazine (Box TV60)
    - 2-40-96. Rachel Rosen studio DeBeers (Box TV60)
    - 2-41-96. Vincent Genn portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-42-96. Mai Lissa Armstrong portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-44-96. Wendy Harrington portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-45-96. Kathryn Schaub portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-48-96. Susan Charbonfau portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-49-96. Paul Trantanella portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-50-96. Kenny Ho portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-51-96. Linda Clasen portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-53-96. Gina Forgele portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-54-96. Michael Hawkins portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-55-96. Scott Hennley portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-56-96. Lisa Micarelli (Box TV60)
    - 2-57-96. Peter Pauker portrait (Box TV60)
    - 2-58,59-96. Blood drive I, II (Box TV60)
    - 2-60-96. Hush Puppy (Box TV60)
    - 2-61-96. Melissa Murphy, Burt Manning (Box TV60)
    - 3-2-96. Vicki Brown portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-4-96. Tom Ferrara portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-5-96. Audrey Del Grosso portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-6-96. State of the Company (Box TV60)
    - 3-8-96. Warner Lambert international group (Box TV60)
    - 3-9-96. Debbie Reiner studio (Box TV60)
    - 3-10-96. Emilie Council portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-11-96. James Tan portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-12-96. Linda Classen portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-13-96. Phil Welsher portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-14-96. Chris Seid portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-15-96. Andrew Fenning studio portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-16-96. Sheron Slater portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-17-96. Jaleh Iranpour portrait studio (Box TV60)
    - 3-18,19-96. Schick party (Box TV60)
    - 3-21-96. Bonnie Mayo portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-22-96. Susan Rizack portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-23-96. Chelsea Chan portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-29-96. John Haskin portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-30-96. Debra Coughlin portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-31-96. Shelly Wattson portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-32-96. Gina Botafuco portrait Direct biographical (Box TV60)
    - 3-24-96. Jim Kloiber Direct biographical (Box TV60)
    - 3-25-96. Rae Loesch Direct biographical (Box TV60)
    - 3-26-96. PDP group 28 prints (Box TV60)
    - 3-27-96. Sheron Slater portrait (Box TV60)
    - 3-27-96. Shelly Broder (Box TV60)
    - 3-28-96. Debbie Curtis portrait studio (Box TV60)
    - 4-1-96. Phillip Conklin portrait (Box TV60)
    - 4-4-96. Chris Soares portrait (Box TV60)
    - 4-8-96. Still life DeBeers (Box TV60)
    - 4-9,10,11,12,13,14,15-96. Scott Keegal, Stuart Keating, Stuart Burkhoff, Kurt Meinen, John Haskin, Barry Shelbourn, Bonnie Mayo, Judy Ritensky (Box TV60)
    - 4-17,18,19-96. Amie Stern, Tim Kane, Stark Kalten (Box TV60)
    - 4-21-96. Health Fair (Box TV60)
    - 4-20,22-96. Entertainment Tonight (Box TV60)
- Oversize Materials
  - Artwork owned by JWT, (17 boxes)
    - Lucchesi, Bruno. Sculpture, circa 1966 (Box OV1)
    - Michaels, Glen. Sculpture, circa 1964 (Box OV1)
  - Awards
    - Gold Effie, 1994 (Box OV1)
  - Corporate Events
    - Board of Directors Meeting, JWT USA, 1980-1986 (Box OV2)
    - Young Tigers Seminar, 1994 (Box OV2)
    - U.S. Professionals Conference, Glen Cove, N.Y., photograph album, 1978 (Box OV3)
    - Chesebrough Pond's USA Meeting, undated (Opaperfolder 1)
    - Dr. Thompson's Academy, 1987 (Box OV3)
    - Messrs. J.W. Thompson (production) Co. Ltd., Creative Dept., 1975 (Box OV3)
    - Lever Brothers Co. 75 year anniversary lifebuoy soap advertisement1977 (Opaperfolder 4)
  - Officers and Staff
    - Griffin, William, circa 1950s (Box OV4)
    - Johnston, Don, 1969-1980 (Box OV4)
    - Owett, Bernie, 1968-1979 (Box OV4)
    - Reber, John Ulrich, circa 1930s (Box OV4)
    - Resor, Stanley Burnet, circa 1949 (Box OV4)
    - Seymour, Dan, 1960s (Box OV4)
    - Strouse, Norman, 1960s, 1986 and undated, (4 folders) (Box OV5)
    - Sutton, Thomas, 1960s (Box OV5)
    - Thompson, J. Walter, 1885, 1910, (2 folders) (Box OV5)
    - Young, James Webb, undated, (2 folders) (Box OV5)
    - Group portrait, undated (Box OV5)
    - Group portrait: JWT Front and Center (employees in military), 1943 (Box OV5)
    - Group portrait, with E.G. Wilson, undated (Box OV5)
    - Photograph album of JWT employees, 1880-1892 (Box OV6)
    - Resor, Helen Landsdowne, undated (Opaperfolder 2)
    - Thompson, J. Walter Commodore portrait (reproduction) (Opaperfolder 7)
    - Thompson, J. Walter portrait (oval frame), undated (Opaperfolder 7, Framed-item 1)
    - Thompson, J. Walter portrait (square frame), undated (Opaperfolder 7, Framed-item 2)
  - Offices
    - New York Office
      - Buildings--244 Madison, 1919, (2 folders) (Box OV7)
      - Buildings--244 Madison, History of the New England Room (Opaperfolder 5)
      - Buildings--23rd Street (Opaperfolder 6)
      - Buildings--466 Lexington, 1981 (Box OV7)
      - Buildings--Greybar Building, 1930s-1947, (5 folders) (Box OV7)
      - Event--Christmas party, 1947 (Box OV7)
      - Event--Field Representative dinner (Box OV7)
      - Event--Oscar Mayer/JWT 30th anniversary photograph album, 1989 (Box OV8)
      - Model/Celebrity photographs (Box OV9)
        - Arden, Eve, undated (Box OV9)
        - Harris, Julie, 1975 (Box OV9)
        - Oneida, Cathy with Bob Crosby, 1966 (Box OV9)
        - Oneida, Cathy with Melvyn Douglas, 1970 (Box OV9)
        - Oneida, Cathy with Firestone, undated (Box OV9)
        - Oneida, Cathy with Halliday, 1972 (Box OV9)
        - Oneida, Cathy with Menuchen, 1973 (Box OV9)
        - Oneida, Cathy with Pinzas, 1958 (Box OV9)
        - Oneida, Cathy with John Cameron Swayze, 1971 (Box OV9)
        - Oneida, Cathy with Robert Young, 1963 (Box OV9)
        - Peerce, Jan, 1964 (Box OV9)
        - Peters, Roberta, 1965 (Box OV9)
        - Tandy, Jessica with Hume Cronin, 1963 (Box OV9)
        - Unknown, by P. Ballantine & Sons, undated (Box OV9)
        - Unknown, envelope marked Liggett Myers, 1964-1965 (Box OV9)
    - Chicago Office
      - Buildings--Wrigley Building interiors, undated (Box OV10-OV11)
      - Events--100th Anniversary photograph albums, 1964 (Box OV12-OV13)
      - Events--50th Anniversary of Chicago office, 1941 (Opaperfolder 3)
      - Events--Eyes on Kraft, undated (Box OV12-OV13)
      - Events--J. Walter Cooks, undated (Box OV12-OV13)
    - Other U.S. Offices
      - Detroit
        - Album of Ford team reception, 1951 (Box OV14)
        - Buildings--Fairlane Park (Dearborn) interior, circa 1975 (Box OV15)
        - Group portraits, 1950s (Box OV15)
        - Group portraits--JWT Ford International Group, 1997 (Box OV15)
      - San Francisco
        - Poster to commemorate opening of office, by Wes Wilson, 1967 (Box OV15)
    - International Offices
      - Australia--Sydney (Box OV16)
        - Buildings--132 Elizabeth Street, 1964, (2 folders) (Box OV16)
      - England--London
        - Buildings--40 Berkeley Square, circa 1962, (3 folders) (Box OV16)
        - Buildings--Bush House, circa 1919 (Box OV16)
        - Client--Kellogg's, circa 1962 (Box OV16)
      - France--Paris
        - Buildings--Time Life Building, circa 1962 (Box OV16)
      - Germany--Frankfurt
        - Buildings--Bockenheimer Landstrasse 104, 1964, (2 folders) (Box OV16)
        - Support Services staff, 1980 (Box OV16)
      - India--Bombay
        - Buildings--Interior views, 1960s (Box OV16)
      - India--Madras
        - Buildings--Exterior views, undated (Box OV16)
      - Italy--Rome
        - Advertising manual, 1951 (Box OV16)
      - Japan--Tokyo
        - Eyes on Thompson poster (J. Walter Thompson in kimono), 1994 (Box OV16)
      - Mexico--Mexico City
        - Group portraits, 1962 (Box OV16)
      - Pakistan--Karachi
        - Buildings--Interior views, undated (Box OV16)
      - Philippines--Manila
        - Buildings--Exterior views, undated (Box OV16)
        - Buildings--Interior views, undated (Box OV16)
      - Puerto Rico--San Juan
        - Buildings--665 Ponce de Leon Avenue, undated (Box OV16)
  - Photographers
    - Bartholomew, Ralph Jr., images for Kodak, 1947-1952 (Box OV17)
      [Ralph Bartholomew, Jr., began his career in advertising as an Assistant Art Director at Batten, Barton, Durstine & Osborn (BBDO). Upon leaving BBDO, he returned to art school and after graduating went to work at the Detroit branch of a large New York studio. In the early 1940s Bartholomew returned to New York to open his own studio in Manhattan, and in 1946 began accepting photographic assignments from JWT. M. Katherine Wiggins, the Art Consultant at JWT, introduced Bartholomew and his work to Fenton Powers, the Art Director on the Kodak account.]
      [Powers assigned Bartholomew to work on campaigns for a variety of products. In 1948 Kodak recognized the need to reach the burgeoning adolescent market with its camera and film products. Among Bartholomew's first assignments were photographs for these teen-directed campaigns. Powers and Thayer Jaccaci, the Kodak Account Executive, chose Bartholomew's photographs for much of the teen-directed advertisements over the next eight years.]
      [In taking the photographs of teenagers, Bartholomew used non-professionals as models, as he preferred their unaffected reactions. Many of the young people were recruited from the public high school in Scarsdale, the town where Bartholomew lived. Settings for the photographs were ones that were familiar to the inexperienced models: the Danbury Fair, Jones Beach, and Scarsdale itself.]
      [This collection of prints date from 1947 to 1952, and originally consisted of 20 tear sheets and proofs; 24 photographs; and one issue of Commercial Camera. The tear sheets and proofs were primarily employed in the teen-directed campaigns. The 24 photographs, consisting of 23 black-and-white prints and one color print, were also used for Kodak advertisements directed toward teenagers. The issue of Commercial Camera (Vol. 1 No. 1, Oct./Nov. 1947) contained an article by Bartholomew, Not Just Because It's Fast. (From original description by Annamarie V. Sandecki, JWT Archives, 1980.)]